Contact

bryanheng26@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bryanheng26 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Presentation Skills
Public Speaking
Leadership

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Chinese (Native or Bilingual)
Malay (Professional Working)

Certifications

Getting Things Done

Leading Projects

Design Thinking: Understanding the Process

Delivery Tips for Speaking in Public Complex Project Tips and Tricks

Honors-Awards

3rd place in Smoke Sensing Robot Challenge

3rd place in Ergonomics Project

Champion for Engineering Multidisciplinary Project

Champion for Chemical Engineering Group Project (Engineering Fair)

Bryan Heng

Chemical Engineering Graduate from Taylor's University Kuala Lumpur

Summary

A Chemical Engineering graduate from Taylor's University. Recipient of full scholarship award under Taylor's University Leadership and Innovation Program (TULIP).

Throughout my academic years I have had the opportunity to take on multiple leadership roles in clubs and societies, together with experience in event planning/organizing with multiple project teams. These extra-curricular involvements have helped me to enhance my communication, management and leadership skills.

Experience

Taylor's University
Research Assistant
August 2019 - September 2019 (2 months)
Selangor, Malaysia

- Continuation of Final Year Research on the topic of "Vulnerability Analysis in Manufacturing Processes" under supervisor.
- Research is about the development of a framework which includes Failure Analysis and a novel Vulnerability Number model to analyse vulnerability in a production line. Framework was applied to a glove manufacturer case study.
- This framework and model act as a decision-making tool to identify which equipment in the process is more vulnerable and therefore requires more protection.

Yokogawa Malaysia Engineer Intern January 2018 - March 2018 (3 months) Selangor, Malaysia

- Generated graphics for Process Control System using Centum VP Software based on Process & Instrumentation Diagram (part of Petronas RAPID Project)

- Assisted senior engineer in performing Factory Acceptance Test (FAT) for Distributed Control System (DCS) alongside clients

SJK (C) Mun Choong Temporary Teacher January 2016 - January 2016 (1 month) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Education

Taylor's University

Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng), Chemical Engineering · (2015 - 2019)

Taylor's University
Foundation degree, Engineering · (2014 - 2015)